Ria-chan, would you like to put that in?
リアちゃん、それ入れてみる?
put in.
入れる
You can use whatever position you like.
好きな体勢でいいからね
ERROR
い けそうな体勢で
I entered.
入った
Did you enter?
入った?
Let's take a look through this scope.
このスコープで覗いてみようと
3、2、
1...
Because everything is in the way and I can't see anything.
す べてを邪魔してて、何かが見えないから
Try taking it out slowly.
ゆっくり出してみて
Take it out slowly?
ゆっくり出して?
Try pulling it out a little.
ちょっと抜いてみて
Put it in again.
また入れる
Let's take it out a little more.
もうちょっと抜いてみよう
Stay in the same position.
そのままの体勢で
3、
2、 1...
3、2、
1...
put in.
入 れる
Yuku
ゆ っ く
Try it out.
り 出してみて
ERROR
できちゃうと思う
What should I do?
どうしよう?
It ends.
終わる
Yes, thank you very much.
はい、ありがとうございました